<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keh-Kuan Sun</title>
    <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keh-Kuan Sun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 22:20:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kehkuansun.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a behavioral and experimental economist studying microeconomic theory and the economics of networks. I am particularly interested in how our individual rationality and its context (be it costly information, social norms, or network structures) affect our choices. I received my Ph.D. in Economics from Washington University in St. Louis. Currently, I am a postdoctoral research associate at the Smith Institute for Political Economy and Philosophy at Chapman University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Publication &amp;ldquo;Habits as Adaptations: An Experimental Study&amp;rdquo;
with Ludmila Matysková, Brian Rogers, and Jakub Steiner, Games and Economic Behavior, Volume 122, July 2020, pp. 391-406 [paper] Working Paper &amp;ldquo;Lying Aversion and Vague Communication: An Experimental Study&amp;rdquo; (revise and resubmit, European Economic Review)
with Stella Papadokonstantaki [poster (AEA2022)] [video][draft]
Using a novel experimental design that allows participants to be vague while at the same time isolating the internal cost of lying from the social identity cost of appearing dishonest, we explore the extent to which these two types of lying costs affect communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiment Summary</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/public_summary/experiment_id/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 22:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/public_summary/experiment_id/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for participating in [[ experiment title ]] on [[ experiment date ]]. We are currently analyzing the data. Please come back to this webpage if you are interested in the results. If you have more questions, please feel free to contact the researchers.
Research Summary TBA
Main Findings TBA
Researchers Keh-Kuan Sun
Postdoctoral Research Associate, Smith Institute for Political Economy and Philosophy, Chapman University.
Email: kesun [at] chapman [dot] edu Edward Honda</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 22:08:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Chapman University: Principles of Microeconomics (Econ 200, Undergraduate):
Fall 2022 [eval] [syllabus]
Fall 2021 [eval] [syllabus] Washington University in St. Louis: Introduction to Microeconomics (Econ 1011, Undergraduate):
Summer 2017 [eval] [syllabus] Behavioral Economics (Econ 305, Undergraduate):
Summer 2018 (cancelled) [syllabus] As teaching assistant, Washington University in St. Louis: Behavioral Economics and Experimental Economics (Econ 404, Undergraduate):
Spring 2017, Spring 2018, Spring 2019 [eval] [eval] Introduction to Macroeconomics:
Fall 2016 As teaching assistant, Yonsei University: Game Theory (Undergraduate, in English): Fall 2012, Spring 2013, Spring 2014, Spring 2015 Economics of Uncertainty (Undergraduate, in English): Spring 2014 Contract Theory (Undergraduate, in English): Fall 2014 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
