<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keh-Kuan Sun</title>
    <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keh-Kuan Sun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kehkuansun.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:59:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Ph.D. Candidate in Economics, Washington University in St. Louis. My primary fields of interest are behavioral and experimental economics, along with the secondary interests in microeconomic theory and economics of networks.
 I come from a multicultural background as a descendant of a Chinese immigrant family in South Korea. Born and raised in a rural town of Korea, my journey began when I first arrived in Kansas as an exchange student in my high school days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:20:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Publication  &amp;ldquo;Habits as Adaptations: An Experimental Study&amp;rdquo; with Ludmila Matysková, Brian Rogers, and Jakub Steiner, Games and Economic Behavior, Volume 122, July 2020, pp. 391-406 [paper] [slides]
(Draft available upon request.)  Job Market Paper  &amp;ldquo;Lying Aversion and Vague Communication: An Experimental Study&amp;rdquo; with Guangying Chen
[abstract]  We study the effect of allowing vague communication on one’s lying behavior using a model of costly lying and provide empirical knowledge through an online experiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://kehkuansun.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:08:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kehkuansun.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>As instructor:  Introduction to Microeconomics (Econ 1011): Summer 2017 [eval] [syllabus] Behavioral Economics (Econ 305): Summer 2018 (cancelled) [syllabus]  As teaching assistant:  Behavioral Economics and Experimental Economics (Econ 404): Spring 2017, Spring 2018, Spring 2019 [eval] [eval] Introduction to Macroeconomics: Fall 2016  Past teaching experience (School of Economics, Yonsei University): As teaching assistant:  Undergraduate Game Theory: Fall 2012, Spring 2013, Spring 2014, Spring 2015 Undergraduate Economics of Uncertainty: Spring 2014 Undergraduate Contract Theory: Fall 2014  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
